let questions = [
    {
    number: 1,
    
    question: "How do you initialize an array in C ",
    answer: "int arr[3] = {1,2,3};",
    options: [
      "int arr[3] = (1,2,3);",
      "int arr(3) = {1,2,3};",
      "int arr[3] = {1,2,3};",
      "int arr(3) = (1,2,3);"
    ]
  },
    
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "With what data structure can a priority queue be implemented more efficiently?",
    answer: "Heap",
    options: [
      "Array",
      "List",
      "Heap",
      "Tree"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 3,
    question: "How many extra nodes are there in Full ternary tree than a complete ternary tree?",
    answer: "Both have same number of nodes",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "Both have same number of nodes"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 4,
    question: "What is the number of vertices of degree 2 in a path graph having n vertices,here n>2.",
    answer: "n-2",
    options: [
      "n-2",
      "n",
      "2",
      "0"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 5,
    question: "What data structure is used when converting an infix notation to prefix notation?",
    answer: "Stack",
    options: [
      "Stack",
      "Queue",
      "B-Trees",
      "Linked-list"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 6,
    question: "Out of the following operators (^, *, +, &, $), the one having highest priority is ",
    answer: "^",
    options: [
      "+",
      "$",
      "^",
      "&"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 7,
    question: "What traversal over trie gives the lexicographical sorting of the set of the strings?",
    answer: "inorder",
    options: [
     "postorder",
      "preorders",
      "inorder",
      "level order"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is the efficient data structure for searching words in dictionaries?",
    answer: "Trie",
    options: [
      "BST",
      "Linked List",
      "Balanced BST",
      "Trie"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 9,
    question: " A circular linked list can be used for?",
    answer: "Both Stack & Queue",
    options: [
      "Stack",
      "Both Stack & Queue",
      "Queue",
      "Neither Stack nor Queue"
    ]
  },

  {
    number: 10,
    question: "How many types of insertion are performed in a binary tree?",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ]
  },
];